targetwoman.com 2018-09-14

# Privacy Policy - TargetWoman

## Privacy Policy of TargetWoman

TargetWoman, an Online Women Publication dedicated to Women, is deeply committed to protecting individual privacy. We respect the privacy of the individuals who visit our portal. We declare here that we will not sell, distribute, lend or part with the collected personal information - if any. This is in consonance with our avowed policy to protect individual privacy. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. The following is a brief declaration of the information gathering and dissemination practices that this web site follows.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.targetwoman.com/tos.html).

**Normal Information:**  
As is normal with all websites, our server collects the usual browser information available when a browser or user agent requests any information from our servers. These are standard in nature and will consist of the following:

  * User IP address 
  * Browser type 
  * Date and time 
  * Requested File 
  * Referrer 
  * Browser capability (for some pages) 

This information is not personally identifying or identifiable. It cannot be used to identify a specific individual. This information helps in improving our services in future by providing accurate statistics to advertisers in the form of aggregated data. If there are any exceptions, there will be a clear disclosure regarding the same. This will give you an opportunity to choose not to participate or provide this information. Our directory section contains links to other websites. When you enter any of these websites, it must be noted that their policies may be materially different from our Privacy policy. 

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

TargetWoman will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

## Disclosure Of Data

## Legal Requirements

TargetWoman may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of TargetWoman
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

## Security Of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx). 

## Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

**Google Analytics**  
Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

## Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

## Children's Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

**Personal Information** :   
We do NOT collect any personal information in our Website except in the Directory section. The information we may collect for submitting to our directory - User name,Email and any other relevant information are strictly for weeding out any spam. We do not sell or redistribute this information to anyone. 

**Contact Information** :  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you should contact the Webmaster through our [contact](http://www.targetwoman.com/contact.html) page. 

The personal information collected from the visitors of our website, including their identity, remains confidential. We respect the law(s) on confidentiality applicable to this website (US) and we will never pass on these data to any third party, unless required by law. Our website does not collect any cookies. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy** :  
We reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time for any reason. Notice of any such changes will be posted as an updated Privacy Policy on this site.
